So here first of all you have to
download the health
insurance mobile app from Google Play Store,
you have to click on it, it takes you to the
Super Top option, here you can see
Super Top Super Top Up, when you click on it, it will
ask you whether you
already have a health insurance policy
or not, so I don't have any policy here,
so here we chose No I don't have
and we will continue, right, here it
gives you the option 22 Super Top Up,
you can see below, I will click on this button,
after that we have to give the details of the family
members in whose name we want to purchase this policy,
so I would
like to purchase this policy in my name and my wife's
name, so I have chosen Self and My Spouse,
if you have a child then you
can click on Sania Doctor, right, here
we go to Next,
after going to the Next option, you will have to mention the family members
here, right, so for example, here
we put myself, it is
40 years old, right, and wife's name
here  But if you take it for two years less, then
this becomes your
30 years right now.
So here this is a material
fact, you have to give disclosure very carefully,
if you have any free
existing disease, then you have to click on this second
option and
tell about your disease. Here when you click
next, you will be asked what
is your disease, you have to explain it, but
if you are fit and fine, like I do
not have any problem, then I will
click here everyone is healthy right and we will click next
here. So here now the first
thing you have to do is the cover of your policy and
while choosing the cover in the super top policy, you have to keep two
things in mind,
how much deductible you want to put in the policy and how much
samishchot you want to take for the super top policy,
right, so whatever deductible you
want here, you have the option of out of pocket cover here,
you will edit it here. Now suppose
I have a policy of ₹4 lakh, so
I have added the dedictable out of pocket cover of ₹4 lakh here.  We have
selected the pocket cover, right, and the
top cover here, we will edit it and bring it
from ₹40 lakh here, you can
see from ₹3 lakh onwards here,
and you can take any top up policy up to ₹3 crore
here, so from ₹1 crore
for example, I want to take a cover of ₹1 crore, right, so ₹4 lakh
with four-layer deductible,
right, I will donate here,
after donating, you can see that
our discounted premium is
reflected here, right, at the top, you can see that there is a
cover of ₹1 crore, there is a dedictable of ₹4 lakh, there are
two members covered in this
and 30% discount, hence, in the policy, you get ₹
867 per month premium,
right, so now we will continue here,
after this, we have to enter the name of the self here, so from ₹1 lakh we change it to my
self, religion,
wife,
right, after that
we have to enter the date of birth, it should match with what we entered earlier,
right, here we have
taken t1 2 years less than ₹1 crore  So let's take this, let's
say 83, right, so it must be a match, so 861,
so let's see what is the premium,
here our premium has increased
because perhaps our actual date of
birth is a little higher,
right, so the premium here becomes 1007
per month, we have to pay here, now you
will see that our annual premium will also be
reflected, so if I have to pay monthly, then
this is free, if I have to pay
annually, then I will do the second option,
my annual premium will come to ₹1287, where
I get a discount of 33%,
right, and we can
easily pay our premium by clicking on the Pay Now OK option here
and purchase this policy,
right, to pay the premium, you can do it on your phone, you can use
any UPI ID, you
can also make your payment through credit or debit card